Records of the National Society Of New England Women, 1895-1988
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. NATIONAL COMMITTEES
  - Program Lending Bureau, list of papers, c. 1956 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - papers, DC, GA, IL, IA, KS (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - papers, MA, MI, MN, MO, NE, NJ, NY (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - papers, NY (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - papers, NY, OH, OR (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - papers, PA, TX, VT, WV,WI, no state (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Tercentennial Committee, report, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- SERIES VI. YEARBOOKS
  - Yearbooks
    - 1910-1911, 1911-1912 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - 1912-1913 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 1915-1916, March 1918 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 1919-1920, 1920-1921 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 1921-1922, 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - 1926-1927, 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 1928-1929, 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 1930-1931, 1931-1932 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - 1932-1933, 1933-1934 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - 1934-1935, 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - 1936-1937, 1937-1938 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - 1938-1939, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 1940-1941, 1942-1943 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - 1943-1944, 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - 1945-1946, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - 1947-1948, 1948, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - 1949-1950, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - 1955-1956 (fragment) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - 1964-1965, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - 1967-1968, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - 1969-1970, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - 1971-1972, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - 1973-1974, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - 1975-1976, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - 1977-1978, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - 1981-1982, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - 1984-1985, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- SERIES VII. NATIONAL MEMBERSHIP APPLICATIONS
  - Applications
    - 0-4484, unbound, incomplete (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 2099-2999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 2618-2974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - 3000-3250 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 3250-3499 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - 3500-3749 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - 3750-3999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 4000-4249 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 4250-4499 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 5000-5249 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 5250-5490 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 5491-5540, unbound (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 5541-5600, unbound (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 5601-5670, unbound (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 5671-5801, unbound (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - 6000-6249 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - 6250-6499 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - 6500-6749 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - 6750-6999 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - 7000-7249 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - 7250-7499 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - 7500-7749 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - 7750-7999 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - 8000-8249 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - 8250-8499 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - 8500-8749 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - 8750-8999 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - 9000-9249 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - 9250-9499 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - 9500-9749 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - 9750-9999 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - 10,000-10,249 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - 10,250-10,499 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - 10,500-10,749 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - 10,750-10,999 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - 11,000-11,249 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - 11,250-11,464 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - 11,465-11,720 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - 11,721-12,018 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - 12,019-12,249 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - 12,250-12,499 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - 12,500-12,749 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - 12,750-12,999 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - 13,000-13,249 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - 13,250-13,499 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - 13,500-13,749 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - 13,750-13,950 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - 13,951-14,099 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - 14,100-14,200 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - 14,201-14,293 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - 14,294-14,420 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - 14,421-14,491 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - 14,492-14,568 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - 14,569-14,705 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - 14,706-14,827 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - 14,828-14,949 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - 14,838 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - 14,950-15,089 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - 15,090-15,209 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - 15,210-15,430 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - 15,431-15,663 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - 15,664-15,757 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - 15,758-15,862 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - 15,863-15,969 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - 15,970-16,031 (Box 41, Folder 65)
    - 16,032-16,112 (Box 41, Folder 66)
    - 16,113-16,155 (Box 41, Folder 67)
    - 16,156-16,194 (Box 41, Folder 68)
    - 16,195-16,261 (Box 42, Folder 69)
    - 16,262-16,349 (Box 42, Folder 70)
    - 16,350-16,407 (Box 42, Folder 71)
    - 16,408-16,449 (Box 42, Folder 72)
    - 16,450-16,511 (Box 43, Folder 73)
    - 16,512-16,572 (Box 43, Folder 74)
    - 16,573-16,634 (Box 44, Folder 75)
    - 16,614 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - 16,635-16,704 (Box 44, Folder 77)
    - 16,705-16,778 (Box 45, Folder 78)
    - 16,779-16,819 (Box 45, Folder 79)
    - 16,820-16,871 (Box 45, Folder 80)
    - 16,872-16,927 (Box 46, Folder 81)
    - 16,928-16,978 (Box 46, Folder 82)
    - 16,971 (Box 46, Folder 83)
    - 16,979-17,021 (Box 46, Folder 84)
    - 17,022-17,065 (Box 47, Folder 85)
    - 17,066-17,105 (Box 47, Folder 86)
    - 17,106-17,152 (Box 47, Folder 87)
    - 17,038 (Box 47, Folder 88)
    - 17,153-17,189 (Box 48, Folder 89)
    - 17,190-17,225 (Box 48, Folder 90)
  - Microfilm, by reel, of membership applications
    - Colonies 5, 7, 10, 14, 17, 18, 2, 3, 6 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Colonies 3, 6, 4, 9, 15, 8 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Colonies #8 (cont.) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Colonies 14, 16; 4000-4295 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Colonies vols. 1-3, 1914-1961 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - 2099-2999; 5000-5249 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - 2618-2974 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - 3000-3249; 4295-4499 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - 3000-3451 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - 3499-3749 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - 3750-3838 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - 3838-3999; 14,201-14,340 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - 5250-5490 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - 5491-5725 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - 6001-6211 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - 6262-6498 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - 6500-6749 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - 6750-6999 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - 7000-7249 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - 7250-7499 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - 7500-7749 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - 7750-7999 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - 8000-8249 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - 8250-8499 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - 8500-8749 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - 8750-8999 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - 9000-9249 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - 9250-9499 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - 9500-9749 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - 9750-9999 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 10,000-10,249 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - 10,250-10,499 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - 10,500-10,749 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - 10,750-10,999 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - 11,000-11,249 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - 11,250-11,464 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - 11,465-11,720 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - 11,721-12,018 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - 12,019-12,249 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - 12,250-12,499 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - 12,500-12,749 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - 12,750-12,999 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - 13,000-13,249 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - 13,250-13,499 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - 13,500-13,749 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - 13,750-14,099 (loose papers) (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - 14,100-14,270 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - 14,341-14,563 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - 14,563-14,819 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - 14,820-14,942 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- SERIES VIII NATIONAL PROOFS
  - Proofs
    - proofs, known
      - Adair, Caroline-12219, Elizabeth Alden Colony (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Adams, Elizabeth-17404, Sarah Josepha Buell Hale Colony (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Amos, J.H.-13416, Kansas City Colony (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Anderson, Grace Perry Wells, Worcester Colony (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Aycrigg, Charlotte Carryl (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Baldwin, Mrs. William Caleb-13527, Chicago Colony (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Barr, Jane-17326, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Bartlett, Helen-13656, Wyckoff Colony (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Baylis, Barbara-17516, Texas Colony (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Beine, Rita-17406, Sarah Josepha Buell Hale Colony (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Bennett, Mrs. F.W., Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Bettisworth, Melissa-17348, Illinois Prairie Colony (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Beveridge, Genevieve, Madison Colony (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Birch, Jean-12765, Pilgrim Colony (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Bitney, Abbie-17458, Carolina Capital Colony (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Blount, Zilpa-13631, Toledo Colony (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Boles, Blanche-13956, Glens Falls Colony (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Bondy, Anna Louise (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Bondy, Bertha Annie Sickly (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Borland, Vivien G.-13351, Akron Colony (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Bowen, Susanne-17296, Lyman Hall Colony (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Bowman, Mrs. Charles Lee-13543, New York City Colony (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Brown, Edith-17345, Wampetuc Colony (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Brown, Ella Maudlin (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Brownell, Daphne-17299, Daytona Beach Colony (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Brownell, Ethel-17555, New Haven Colony (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Bulkley, Laura-13204, Topeka Colony (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Burhite, Norlayne-17525, Wampetuc Colony (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Burke, Polly-13143, Rochester Colony (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Burns, Lorretta-17258, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Burr, Edna-13921, Montclair Colony (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Campbell, Mary-17350, Lyman Hall Colony (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Capps, Lois-17342, Illinois Prairie Colony (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - Carroll, Dorothy-17336, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Carvell, Constance-17357, Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Cary, Alice-17455, Daytona Beach Colony (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Chaplin, Anna, Golden Gate Area Colony (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Colburn, Bertha-13363, Colony of the Oranges (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Cone, Lois-13136, Topeka Colony (Box 50, Folder 39)
      - Conlon, Alice-17253, Portland Colony (Box 50, Folder 40)
      - Cook, Patricia-17563, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Cornish, Cressida-17284, Texas Colony (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Cowan, Mrs. Jerome Palmer-13985, Hartford Colony (Box 50, Folder 43)
      - Curtius, Catherine-17513, Oklahoma Colony (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Dickinson, Alice Howard-13505, Worcester Colony (Box 50, Folder 45)
      - Dickinson, Florence-11940, Daytona Beach Colony (Box 50, Folder 46)
      - d'Olier, Georgina-13891, Rochester Colony (Box 50, Folder 47)
      - Dorman, Mrs. Wilmer-13579, Merrimack Valley Colony (Box 50, Folder 48)
      - Dottling, Thelma Emmaline-16795, Hohokam Colony (Box 50, Folder 49)
      - Driscoll, Lucile-17377, Rockford Colony (Box 50, Folder 50)
      - Dunnick, Elsie (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Durocher, Dora Van Viack (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Easterbrooks, Ellen Colby, New York City Colony (Box 51, Folder 53)
      - Ellenwood, Cecilia-13077, Syracuse Colony (Box 51, Folder 54)
      - Elliot, Jane-17265, Grace Sherman Livermore Colony (Box 51, Folder 55)
      - Evans, Ann-17378, Love Samborne Graham Colony (Box 51, Folder 56)
      - Fairfield, Genevieve-17275, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 57)
      - Farnham, Ethel H.-13784, Buffalo Colony (Box 51, Folder 58)
      - Fell, Anna, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 59)
      - Flint, Esther M. (Box 51, Folder 60)
      - Forster, Helen Decker-13706, Tampa Bay Colony (Box 51, Folder 61)
      - Fowle, Elizabeth, Mississippi Valley Colony (Box 51, Folder 62)
      - Franklin, Helen-13788, Topeka Colony (Box 51, Folder 63)
      - Frith, Lillian-17451, Sarah Josepha Buell Hale Colony (Box 51, Folder 64)
      - Frye, May Irma Jewett-9787, St. Petersburg Colony (Box 51, Folder 65)
      - Gildersleeve, Charlotte Rhodes-14053, New York City Colony (Box 51, Folder 66)
      - Gould, Edith-13451, Worcester Colony (Box 51, Folder 67)
      - Graham, Margeret Howk-13103, Chicago Colony (Box 51, Folder 68)
      - Gude, Elizabeth-17344, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 69)
      - Haney, Lucille-17574, Blue Grass Colony (Box 51, Folder 70)
      - Harrill, Mrs. Jacques William-13542, Phyllis Lyman Colony (Box 51, Folder 71)
      - Hatcher, Patricia-17371, Texas Colony (Box 51, Folder 72)
      - Hayes, Ethel-13593, Chicago Colony (Box 51, Folder 73)
      - Henderson, Martha-17501, Illinois Prairie Colony (Box 51, Folder 74)
      - Henshaw, Ruth-17558, Coral Gables Colony (Box 51, Folder 75)
      - Hetzler, Meryde-17422, Rockford Colony (Box 51, Folder 76)
      - Hill, Anna-13735, Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 51, Folder 77)
      - Hillery, Viletta-17349, Illinois Prairie Colony (Box 51, Folder 78)
      - Hinks, Marjorie-13943, Redford Farmington Colony (Box 51, Folder 79)
      - Holmes, Mary-17485 (Box 51, Folder 80)
      - Huffington, Lona-17557, Rockford Colony (Box 51, Folder 81)
      - Hunt, M.B. (Box 51, Folder 82)
      - Ivy, Cecile-17561, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 83)
      - Jackson, Helen-17414, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 84)
      - Jacobs, Lois-17466 (Box 51, Folder 85)
      - Jenkins, Rachel-17554, Eunice Mather Williams Colony (Box 51, Folder 86)
      - Jewett, Edna-17566, Essex County Colony (Box 51, Folder 87)
      - Johnson, Mrs. Luel-13707, Rochester Colony (Box 51, Folder 88)
      - Jordan, Henrietta-17325, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 51, Folder 89)
      - Kellam, Gayle-CR6125, Golden Gate Area Colony (Box 51, Folder 90)
      - Kneass, Margaret-17556, Portland Colony (Box 51, Folder 91)
      - Lack, Ella-14062, Montclair Colony (Box 52, Folder 92)
      - LaHue, Marsha-17465, Daytona Beach (Box 52, Folder 93)
      - Lange, Barbara-13698, Madison Colony (Box 52, Folder 94)
      - Lass, Natalie, Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 52, Folder 95)
      - Latham, Irene-13506, Member-at-Large (Box 52, Folder 96)
      - Leahy, Helen-17577, Mt. Washington Colony (Box 52, Folder 97)
      - Lemmer, Lucille-15168, Chicago Colony (Box 52, Folder 98)
      - Lindley, Rosemary-17410, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 99)
      - Lindsey, Rachel-17412, Oklahoma Colony (Box 52, Folder 100)
      - Logan, Leila-13206, Topeka Colony (Box 52, Folder 101)
      - Lombard, Marvilha-17428, Lyman Hall Colony (Box 52, Folder 102)
      - Manning, Ann-17286, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 103)
      - Mansell, Lillian (Box 52, Folder 104)
      - Martin, Elizabeth-17327, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 105)
      - Martin, Georgia-13971, New York City Colony (Box 52, Folder 106)
      - Mason, Mrs. Nicholas P.-13654, Utica Colony (Box 52, Folder 107)
      - Mattei, Rita-17470, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 108)
      - McDonald, Marian-15102, Wampetuc Colony (Box 52, Folder 109)
      - Meeks, Pauline-17494, Coral Gables Colony (Box 52, Folder 110)
      - Meserve, Elinor-13729, Boston Colony (Box 52, Folder 111)
      - Millbrook, Minnie-13111, Member-at-Large (Box 52, Folder 112)
      - Milne, Edith-13879, New York City Colony (Box 52, Folder 113)
      - Minton, Martha-17564, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 114)
      - Mixer, Lois (Box 52, Folder 115)
      - Moody, Lois-17335, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 52, Folder 116)
      - Moore, Lillian Irene (Box 52, Folder 117)
      - Morgan, Mildred-17484 (Box 52, Folder 118)
      - Muncy, Elisha Louise-6144J, Ann Arbor Colony (Box 52, Folder 119)
      - Munn, Margaret-17263, Buffalo Colony (Box 52, Folder 120)
      - Murray, Phelicia-17567, Essex County Colony (Box 52, Folder 121)
      - Nelson, Olive-13882, Chicago Colony (Box 52, Folder 122)
      - Newbegin, Jean-17565, Essex County Colony (Box 52, Folder 123)
      - Noble, Ruth-13311, New York City Colony (Box 52, Folder 124)
      - Norton, Ethel May-13276, Chicago Colony (Box 52, Folder 125)
      - O'Neal, Virginia-17559, Mt. Washington Colony (Box 52, Folder 126)
      - Page, Lila-13358, Akron Colony (Box 52, Folder 127)
      - Patrick, Betty-17518, Portland Colony (Box 52, Folder 128)
      - Perrin, Ellen-17562, Member-at-Large (Box 52, Folder 129)
      - Pfeiffer, Ruth-17533, Texas Colony (Box 52, Folder 130)
      - Phillips, Gladys Elizabeth-13288, Golden Gate Area Colony (Box 52, Folder 131)
      - Radenz, Elizabeth Anne Redfield-13184, Topeka Colony (Box 53, Folder 132)
      - Raines, Ruth Virginia, Columbus Colony (?) (Box 53, Folder 133)
      - Rawell, Margaret-17292, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 53, Folder 134)
      - Reynolds, Shirley-17522, Wampetuc Colony (Box 53, Folder 135)
      - Rice, Lula V.-14107, Texas Colony (Box 53, Folder 136)
      - Rice, Nettie Belle-13745, Santa Monica Colony (Box 53, Folder 137)
      - Riddle, Elizabeth-17391, Oklahoma Colony (Box 53, Folder 138)
      - Ross, Martha, Blue Grass Colony (Box 53, Folder 139)
      - Sanders, Clara-13597, Syracuse Colony (Box 53, Folder 140)
      - Schaefer, Helen-17571, Pinellas Colony (Box 53, Folder 141)
      - Schober, Flourine-13133, Topeka Colony (Box 53, Folder 142)
      - Seager, Mary-13995, Chicago Colony (Box 53, Folder 143)
      - Seaton, Ida Willis-13314, Phyllis Lyman Colony (Box 53, Folder 144)
      - Severson, Sonnet, Member-at-Large (Box 53, Folder 145)
      - Shaekelford, Bertha Pursel (Box 53, Folder 146)
      - Sill, Helen-13093, Ann Arbor Colony (Box 53, Folder 147)
      - Smith, Billie-17268, Texas Colony (Box 53, Folder 148)
      - Smith, Katherine(?)-17276, Maryland Colony (Box 53, Folder 149)
      - Smith, Mary Dorland-13481, Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 53, Folder 150)
      - Snyder, Mrs. Claude-13286, Evanston Colony (Box 53, Folder 151)
      - Spake, Georgia-17552, Elizabeth Chase Fowler Colony (Box 53, Folder 152)
      - Sperry, Loraine-13490, Golden Gate Area Colony (Box 53, Folder 153)
      - Sterling,-17317, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 53, Folder 154)
      - Stewart, Bertha-14087, Glens Falls Colony (Box 53, Folder 155)
      - Stewart, Katherine-17419, Oklahoma Colony (Box 53, Folder 156)
      - Stewart, Mae-13561, Daytona Beach Colony (Box 53, Folder 157)
      - Stewart, Mildred-13156, Brooklyn Colony (Box 53, Folder 158)
      - Studley, Mary M. (Box 53, Folder 159)
      - Swadley, Helen Marie (Box 53, Folder 160)
      - Sweet, Cynthia-13612, Poughkeepsie Colony (Box 53, Folder 161)
      - Tarantelli, Edythe (Box 53, Folder 162)
      - Toscano, Margaret-17576, John Hall Colony (Box 53, Folder 163)
      - Turner, Dorothy-17411, Sarah Josepha Buell Hale Colony (Box 53, Folder 164)
      - Vetter, Mrs. Earl-13917, Glens Falls Colony (Box 53, Folder 165)
      - Wallace, Mrs. Frederick R.-13558, Syracuse Colony (Box 53, Folder 166)
      - Warren, Alice F. (Box 53, Folder 167)
      - Webster, Lillian Coon-13163, Pilgrim Colony (Box 53, Folder 168)
      - Welles, Linda (Box 53, Folder 169)
      - Whitehead, Caroline-17418, Deacon John Tenney Colony (Box 53, Folder 170)
      - Whitney, Irma-13599, Montclair Colony (Box 53, Folder 171)
      - Whitney, Virginia (Box 53, Folder 172)
      - Williams, Lillian-13663, Cape Cod Colony (Box 53, Folder 173)
      - Wilson, Margaret, Elizabeth Chase Fowler Colony (Box 53, Folder 174)
      - Witt, Eleanor-17421, Rockford Colony (Box 53, Folder 175)
      - Wolf, Brooksie-17361, Texas Colony (Box 53, Folder 176)
      - Wonso, Grace-17569, Chicago Colony (Box 53, Folder 177)
      - Wood, Lois (Box 53, Folder 178)
      - Woods, Norma Hoblit-13142, Chicago Colony (Box 53, Folder 179)
      - Worthau, Addie T. Glenn (Box 53, Folder 180)
      - Wright, Helen M.-13960, Montclair Colony (Box 53, Folder 181)
      - Zabenko, Cornelia-17449, Sarah Josepha Buell Hale Colony (Box 53, Folder 182)
    - proofs, unknown (by family name)
      - Aiken;Jerome;Jeromes (Box 54, Folder 183)
      - Allen; Clay (Box 54, Folder 184)
      - Allen, George A. (Box 54, Folder 185)
      - Allen, Maud B. (Box 54, Folder 186)
      - Avery; Smith (Box 54, Folder 187)
      - Ayers, Myrtle C. (Box 54, Folder 188)
      - Barchard, Ruth Berry (Box 54, Folder 189)
      - Batty, Marion G. (Box 54, Folder 190)
      - Bullock (Box 54, Folder 191)
      - Cady, Mrs. Harold H. (Box 54, Folder 192)
      - Camp; Cornelius; Strickland (Box 54, Folder 193)
      - Carr; Gilbert; Smith (Box 54, Folder 194)
      - Cesman (Box 54, Folder 195)
      - Crissey (Box 54, Folder 196)
      - Ellis (Box 54, Folder 197)
      - French; Jordan (Box 54, Folder 198)
      - French; Wortham (Box 54, Folder 199)
      - Green (Box 54, Folder 200)
      - Harris; Fiske (Box 54, Folder 201)
      - Hawkes (Box 54, Folder 202)
      - Hawkes, Susan (Box 54, Folder 203)
      - Hulburt (Box 54, Folder 204)
      - Jaquith (Box 54, Folder 205)
      - Jennings (Box 54, Folder 206)
      - Johnson; Miller (Box 54, Folder 207)
      - Keeler; Wood (Box 54, Folder 208)
      - Knapp (Box 54, Folder 209)
      - Laughlin; Sanders (Box 54, Folder 210)
      - Liddle (Box 54, Folder 211)
      - Merrit (Box 54, Folder 212)
      - Morse, Mrs. James M. (Box 54, Folder 213)
      - Parkhurst (Box 54, Folder 214)
      - Peckham (Box 54, Folder 215)
      - Perkins (Box 54, Folder 216)
      - Phelps, Chicago Colony (Box 54, Folder 217)
      - Roberts; Snow (Box 54, Folder 218)
      - Sargeant, Eli (Box 54, Folder 219)
      - Sheldon (Box 54, Folder 220)
      - Steadwell; Strobeck; Van Brocklen (Box 54, Folder 221)
      - Strong, Mrs. Weltha (Box 54, Folder 222)
      - Sutton; Walbridge (Box 54, Folder 223)
      - Taylor (Box 54, Folder 224)
      - Taylor; William (Box 54, Folder 225)
      - Thorpe (Box 54, Folder 226)
      - Tripp (Box 54, Folder 227)
      - Wanzer (Box 54, Folder 228)
      - Waugh, Lillian E. (Box 54, Folder 229)
      - Whipple (Box 54, Folder 230)
      - fragments (Box 54, Folder 231)
- SERIES IX. NATIONAL CARD INDEXES
  - Ancestor Cards
    - A-BLI (Box 55)
    - BLO-CH (Box 56)
    - CI-DO (Box 57)
    - DR-GL (Box 58)
    - GO-HOP (Box 59)
    - HOR-LI (Box 60)
    - LO-N (Box 61)
    - O-RI (Box 62)
    - RO-STE (Box 63)
    - STI-WEB (Box 64)
    - WEC-Z (Box 65)
  - Membership Cards
    - A-BEN (Box 66)
    - BER-CAM (Box 67)
    - CAN-CU (Box 68)
    - D-FE (Box 69)
    - FI-G (Box 70)
    - HA-HO (Box 71)
    - HU-K (Box 72)
    - L-MAR (Box 73)
    - MAS-O (Box 74)
    - P-RIC (Box 75)
    - RIC-SMIN (Box 76)
    - SMITH-TH (Box 77)
    - TI-WH (Box 78)
    - WI-Z (Box 79)
- SERIES X. COLONIES
  - ALBANY, NY COLONY
    - General, constitution, 1913, by-laws 1915 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - AMSTERDAM, NY COLONY
    - General, by-laws, undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - minutes, 1928-1929 (Box 80, Folder 3)
        - 1948-1964 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Officers, Registrar, annual reports, 1949-1967 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - correspondence, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - membership lists, 1948-1955 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - ANNE BRADSTREET, CA COLONY
    - General, constitution and by-laws, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Officers, General, correspondence (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Secretary, Treasurer, correspondence, financial records, 1940-1947 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Registrar, correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 80, Folder 11)
        - membership list, undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - AUGUSTA, ME COLONY